I didn't kill him.
What will it take for you to believe me?
Lately, have you been losing things you want
and things you don't want keep
pestering you?
You'll know when the time comes.
-18 degrees?
The Pen Fairy led me to the cold storage?
Wong Sai-lung?
You again, Mr. Chan?
Sister Fong!
Stay away from me!
Calm down. Don't get the wrong idea.
I did not! Sylvia told me
I'll find the uniform in -18 degrees
and run into the killer, you!
If I killed him,
would I be stupid enough to stay
and get caught?
I went inside to see if the killer
was hiding.
Don't try to con me again.
You said you needed the uniform for filming.
But I saw you in Chin Tai-fu's room
wearing the uniform.
If I didn't see the gun and tossed it,
you would have gotten me in big trouble.
You should stick to housekeeping
and leave the gun alone.
Luckily, I was vigilant
and got away by promising Chin Tai-fu
to kill Wong Sai-lung instead.
So you killed Wong Sai-lung!
Hello, anyone out there?
I told you I didn't do it.
What will it take for you to believe me?
Definitely not by pointing a gun at me.
OK...I'll put it down.
Believe me now?
Yes, I promised to kill Wong Sai-lung,
but when I came in,
someone else already beat me to it.
If you didn't kill him, who did?
When I was approaching the cold storage,
I saw someone in housekeeping uniform
walked away.
Was he wearing a cap?
How did you know?
I think I saw him.
Was he the killer?
Wait...you're also in uniform.
It could have been you.
Look again. Mine had no stains.
Chin Tai-fu took the one I was wearing.
Luckily, I found another one in the
changing room.
If Chin Tai-fu took yours,
and I got the second one from Mrs. Chin,
the third one...the killer took it?
You finally believe me!
Fullcoin landed me in deep trouble.
I have wanted to kill the guy.
But someone else killed him
and I must kiss the money goodbye.
He's dead and bullets bear no marks.
Just tell Chin Tai-fu you got the job done.
You're vicious.
You pay me hush money,
I won't squeal on you.
You know why a woman like me
can be so vicious?
Because I'm also a Fullcoin victim.
My son is still in the hospital.
Chin Tai-fu filed a complaint against me
and I'm about to get canned.
You're worse off than I am.
Think no more.
It's rare that he died in a cold place.
I'll get you some gloves,
wrap up the body like cold cut.
This should do the trick.
Thanks, Mr. Chin!
Hey, what's your name.
Yes?
You've worked hard all day.
Get your pal in here for a bite.
No thanks, we're not hungry.
You need to relax a bit.
Go get him.
What's up?
Rats! He wants us in there to
help him relax.
What?
The stud cupcake is not enough?
Now he wants 3P?
What now?
If anything goes wrong,
I'll punch his lights out.
Great!
Don't just stand there. Eat something.
As professional bodyguards,
we must always remain vigilant.
Won't sit down and eat.
Red wine?
As professional bodyguards,
we're not supposed to drink.
How dutiful of you!
I'll drink the wine, you can have tea. OK?
Yes, Mr. Chin.
Cheers!
Thomas! Thomas!
Mr. Chin, if you have the need,
I'll get the white-haired stud cupcake.
I sell my professionalism,
let's not overdo this.
Here!
He took his clothes off.
Mr. Chin must be a cross-dresser.
Mr. Chin, what are you doing?
You said not to overdo it.
Let's get started.
I meant to say call it a day. Not overdo it.
Be quiet, I'll be gentle. Come on...
You're crazy! I quit!
Hey...
Remember what I told you?
Yes, after I collect the money,
find a place to hide the gun.
But why must I do that?
Wong Sai-lung's body will be
discovered sooner or later.
The cops will look into his connections
with Chin Tai-fu.
If we plant the gun in his room,
let him take the rap for it.
You think you can frame him by doing that?
Though he has a motive,
he's followed by two bodyguards,
they probably can't prove he did it.
If he paid you for the hit,
he could have hired a second hitman.
True.
Chin Tai-fu and Wong Sai-lung
are rich but heartless.
Plenty of people want them dead.
That's why we must act fast.
If the other hitman beat us to him,
he'll walk away with the golden egg.
Darn! I forgot my phone.
What? I was right about it!
He stole the third uniform.
Hey...
Chin Tai-fu?
Oh dear, I knocked out the golden egg.
What now?
Take him into his room.
Hurry...come on!
Get in!
Why didn't you look before you hit him?
How would I know he wore my uniform?
What happened out there?
Who cares? Put the gun in a safe place.
Before Chin Tai-fu wakes up,
I'm taking the uniform.
OK!
All set?
While Chin Tai-fu is unconscious, wait here.
Hey...you think I can do this alone?
You did the job,
you should stay and collect your money.
I can't be here.
What are you doing?
Mr. Chin called me to clean up.
Sorry, Mr. Chin. I fell asleep.
You again?
Yes, Mr. Chin asked me to clean the room.
Can I help you?
Carry on with Mr. Chin...
I mean carry on with helping Mr. Chin.
Hello, Mr. Chin.
Bloody hell, you took my clothes off?
And conked me on the head?
No, I'm just reporting back to you.
For what?
I exceeded my target.
Here!
Sai-lung, you weasel!
You want to kill me? Go to Hell!
Wait...did you see who hit me?
I think...one of Brother Kui's boys...
Whoever conked me on the head...
you did a good job.
I'll transfer the money to you.
Mr. Chin, my account has been frozen.
Can you pay cash?
Who would carry $1M in cash?
I'll write you a cheque,
you can fill out the name.
A few minutes in bed is what I make
in a few years?!
I have done nothing wrong since
I got married.
With a misunderstanding like that,
my wife is likely to kill me.
Hello, Mr. Chin.
You have been pacing around for a while.
Can I help you?
I'm not in anybody's way.
I'm not allowed to pace up and down
the hotel lobby?
That's not what I mean.
Your wife just called room service,
and ordered the most expensive wine
in our hotel,
and the most expensive dish
on the a la carte menu.
I saw you pacing up and down,
I just thought maybe I can be of service.
How much was the bill?
$23,000 in total.
Oh my God!
Nothing like the wrath of a pissed wife.
I better go up and keep her company.
Of course.
Wait...it's not resolved.
If she asked me again, what can I tell her?
She didn't believe I sold a gun.
After all, I'm worried about the money.
If I found money to cover up the losses,
I'll have nothing to worry about.
GHB, cross-dresser...
Luckily, he just finished with the
white-haired stud cupcake.
But who knows when he'll have the urge.
I don't know how I can go on with this job.
Hey!
Mr. Chin?
Are you awake?
Yes.
You don't look like you can protect me.
I'll pay you for another month. You may go.
Great!
Hi! Is Mr. Chin inside?
I have a business proposal for him.
Mr. Chin is waiting for you.
Just knock on the door.
He really needs you. Good luck.
The clown from next door?
Mr. Chin!
Hey, Mr. Chin...
Are you OK, Boss?
You traitor! You took money
from Sai-lung, right?
I hurried back as soon as I got your call.
Then what took you so long?
I went up north to find out who
took the order.
Since I had time to spare,
I had a bit of fun on the side.
You went whoring when
your Boss is in danger?
Are you out of your mind?
I found out a hitman syndicate
is after you.
(Yip Wing-kei)
Tie him up.
Brother Kei? It's Fu.
How about we clean the slate?
I'll pay you back the money you lost
in Fullcoin.
Just hear me out...
The guy you hired to kill me
is now in my room.
Either you take my money,
and guarantee me and family
will live happily ever after,
or else, if anything should happen to me,
I guarantee I'll use my entire fortune
to kill you.
Good, I'm glad you understand.
Bye!
Feed him to the dogs.
Got it..
Sai-lung is dead.
The Showbiz King is sorted out.
Time for a drink.
Bloody hell!
I'm sorry, Mr. Chin.
It's OK. Come here.
You have the guts. You saved my neck.
You flatter me. As long as you're OK.
Come here...you have a business proposal?
Yes, I have...
OK...send the proposal to my secretary.
I'll give you $10M.
Thank you, Mr. Chin...
Don't thank me, thank your wife.
Natasha knows Mr. Chin?
Thank her for what?
Let's try the bed.
It's so comfy.
You must have a touching story to tell.
Try me.
Believe it or not, I wasn't cheating on you.
What were you doing, sneaking around
in that room?
While we were having dinner,
I found a gun on the trolley.
I decided to sell it.
So I grabbed the towels and tried the gun
in another room.
That's brilliant. You're such a lecher!
How could you come up with a lie like that?
Then how do you explain
why Chin Tai-fu was willing to
invest in my company.
When I thanked him, he said
I should thank you.
I pretended to have an affair with him
so he could ditch his bodyguards
and leave the room.
To thank me for a favor,
he gave me his key card so I can
take pictures of the Ambassador Suite
and show them to my besties.
Are you so vain?
You cheat on your husband
in order to take pictures?
So you can cheat on me
but I can't take pictures?
I don't mind you cheating on me.
As long as I put a stop to it.
What do you mean, Chin Chi-tat?
You want a divorce?
Chin Chi-tat...
Open the door!
Hello, Boss?
Arrange for my wife to come home.
Get the bellboy to come up and help me pack.
Yes, I'm leaving.
I can't believe that guy would pay us, yeah!
How much was it?
$1M.
$1M?
How do you spell your name?
How could you, Silver Fox?
Why are you putting my name down?
How else can we deposit the cheque?
A hired hit is a big deal.
I'm in big trouble when the cops
start to investigate.
My account has been frozen.
We give up the money?
Ask him for cash, you idiot!
Who would walk around with $1M cash?
I'll write down Chit Chat Kui's name.
I should cut him a share.
Punks are not to be trusted.
Don't cut him in, he'll get greedy.
Write down my name.
When the bank opens tomorrow,
we'll deposit the cheque.
I'll keep the cheque, we'll split it 50/50.
It's payable to you,
you won't need to worry about me
running off.
Is that what you think of me?
My heart has gone off to the $500K.
It's so hard to come to work
after you won the first prize.
There! I finally found you!
That witch can't fire me anymore.
Where's the uniform?
What is this?
You again, Mr. Chan?
Silver Fox left you in Chin Tai-fu's room.
Hell! Someone will find you eventually.
How did the gun end up in the
laundry cart?
Someone must have touched this gun.
What happened in the hotel?
I know so much, the cops will catch on.
I better run.
You're not firing me, I quit.
I have money now.
Two down, one to go.
You can't accuse me of theft.
You're always on my case.
Bloody Yu Lo, I can't stand you. I quit.
I will tell management you framed me.
Bloody witch!
Honey...I'm sorry.
You're the only one I love.
I intend to die with you!
Chan Lai-sa, what were you thinking?
You had an affair with a rich man
and wanted to ditch me.
Hell, you took the toothpaste
so I can't even brush my teeth!
Brother Bo!
What?
We have a new case.
Billionaire Chin Tai-fu was found dead
in a hotel room.
After his body was sent to the hospital,
they found something suspicious
about his death.
That's why they passed the case to us
to follow up.
Yes, Sir!
The estimated time of death
was between 11 p.m. and 1 a.m.
The cause of death was the explosion
of the pacemaker
blew up his lungs.
Except for a flat wound of 1.5cm in diameter
on his inner thigh,
there were no other wounds on is body.
That's a rare way to die.
Why would the pacemaker explode?
The first person to find Chin Tai-fu's
body was his chauffeur...
Mr. Chin...
The last time he spoke to Chin Tai-fu
was last night at 11:55 p.m.
Mr. Chin!
Boss!
My Boss is dead!
What?
The doors were locked. What happened?
Ms. Yu, what's the occupancy on this floor?
This is the top floor of our hotel.
We only have two suites on this floor.
According to our record,
a couple checked into the Executive Suite
next door.
They checked out three hours ago.
We got something.
That looks like a stun gun.
Did the killer use a stun gun
on Chin Tai-fu,
and the pacemaker exploded?
Then he ditched the stun gun.
Maybe the killer gave Chin Tai-fu a shot
to knock him out.
Then used the stun gun to blow up
the pacemaker.
The wound on the inner thigh was flat.
That didn't look like a wound from a needle.
The power of the stun gun is not enough
to blow up the pacemaker.
Brother Bo, Chin Tai-fu's chauffeur
Roy is here.
How can I help you, officers?
Before Chin Tai-fu died,
did you notice anything unusual?
Not too long before the Boss died,
a white-haired man barged inside
and tried to kill him.
Luckily, I came back just in time
to protect the Boss.
What happened to the white-haired man?
He got away.
The case found under the sofa
was probably brought in by
the white-haired man?
After the man got away,
did Chin Tai-fu have any unusual behavior?
After the killer left,
he probably felt there was no more threat.
He wanted to go home.
He asked me to get help with his luggage.
I can't believe he died
while I stepped away.
A white-haired man
barged in here to commit murder.
He even brought a weapon.
He's probably a professional hitman.
I suspect Wong Sai-lung hired the hit.
If Wong Sai-lung hired the hit,
after the hitman failed,
did he come back for a second attempt?
Or did Wong Sai-lung decide to kill
Chin Tai-fun himself?
Brother Bo, we suspect Wong Sai-lung
hired the hit on Chin Tai-fu.
But now that he's dead,
we have no more leads.
Wong Sai-lung may be dead,
it doesn't mean our deduction is wrong.
He was shot.
Was the killer the white-haired man?
If the killer had a gun,
why didn't he just shoot Chin Tai-fu?
Was there more than one killer?
What? Another body?
F&B found the body, when they
went to the cold storage for frozen meat.
We're finished.
Hotel de Maze became Hotel Double Homicide.
Did you spot anyone suspicious
these last two days?
Yes! Law Siu-fong from housekeeping.
She has a poor record
and was caught stealing from the hotel.
Yesterday, she was acting weird,
she begged me not to fire her,
but at the end of her shift,
she tendered her resignation.
That's her.
Brother Bo, we got something on CCTV.
This white-haired guy
is probably the hitman mentioned by
Chin Tai-fu's chauffeur.
Who is this white-haired killer?
Why did he want to kill Chin Tai-fu
but turned around and killed Wong Sai-lung?
Wu Sir, go check out
anyone who had close contact with
Wong Sai-lung and Chin Tai-fu,
find out about their relationship.
Ming, question the hotel staff,
especially F&B and housekeeping.
See if they have seen the white-haired guy
within hotel premises.
Got it, Brother Bo.
King, check the CCTVs near the hotel.
See if any of them recorded the
white-haired guy and Law Siu-fong.
Got it!
1...2...3...4...5...6...
other than fake money,
I have never seen so many digits
on a cheque.
Hello, Ms. Yu?
I saw Sister Fong with a white-haired man
queuing up in the bank.
Once we deposit this cheque,
my life will be completely changed.
What? It's Chin Tai-fu!
Chin Tai-fu is here?
Where is Chin Tai-fu?
He's dead.
Chin Tai-fu is dead?
Yes!
(Chin Tai-fu found dead in hotel)
If he's dead, what about our cheque?
We better not touch the money.
No? We're next.
Chin Tai-fu died in the hotel.
We're in trouble if we touch the money.
Let's go!
No...
What? Wong Sai-lung who was in charge
of Fullcoin is dead too?
They found Wong Sai-lung's body. Let's go.
This is killing me.
The money is almost ours.
If we took it, we would have been busted.
They'll pin the murders on us
and we'll never clear our names.
Why are we involved?
This cheque is the evidence.
It's not safe to keep it, let's toss it.
No! Maybe in six months,
when things have died down, we can cash it.
Don't be so naive.
You think the cops are stupid?
Not until they catch the killer,
we'll never be off the hook.
Let's just rip the cheque.
Don't kill it.
We're in deep trouble if we don't.
Kill what?
This...see? Don't call the Police.
We're tearing up the cheque. Gone!
We can always make more money.
Don't look so sad.
Those men are staring at us.
They should be cops.
Run...
I'll lure them away.
What?
Your son is in the hospital. He needs you.
You can't get busted.
What about you? If you were caught,
what about you wife and child?
They don't need me. Go!
Right!
Silver Fox, stop!
Cheung Tin-fai, did you sneak into
Chin Tai-fu's room and killed him?
I went inside and made a deal with him.
Shall I spill the beans to prove
my innocence?
You took $500K.
I'll double that and pay you $1M.
Take care of it for me.
I have long wanted to kill Wong Sai-lung.
You're on!
We checked all the CCTV,
we have enough evidence.
Once we arrest the chambermaid,
you can get ready to go to jail.
They suspect Sister Fong.
But she had nothing to do with this.
I better not spill the beans on her.
OK, I'll tell you.
At first, I took the order to kill
Chin Tai-fu.
I disguised as a housekeeper
to get inside the room.
Where did you get the uniform?
I stole it.
You acted alone? No accomplice?
Yes, but before I got into his room,
I lost the gun.
You said you didn't kill Chin Tai-fu
the first time.
Did you go back in a few hours
to make a second attempt?
Chin Tai-fu offered me double
the money to kill Wong Sai-lung,
why would I kill him?
Wong Sai-lung asked me to meet him
at the cold storage,
to give me the gun.
I decided to kill him right then and there.
But I was too late.
He was shot twice when I arrived.
Twice? Wong Sai-lung was shot three times.
When I picked up the gun, I was scared.
I dropped it and it went off
and shot Wong Sai-lung's body.
You're a professional hitman,
how could you be so scared to drop the gun?
I didn't know someone shot him twice
in the head.
We saw from the CCTV you were following
Wong Sai-lung,
then you went inside the cold storage.
How do you explain that?
That wasn't me.
Can't tell the body shape from a top shot.
Yes, the Boss is dead.
I just finished giving a statement.
Excuse me...
What is it, Sir?
We caught the white-haired hitman,
can you identify him for us?
What? You caught him?
Sir, it's not him.
They can't pin it on me.
Shouldn't have told them so much.
Thank you.
See? I told you I didn't follow
Wong Sai-lung.
I didn't kill Chin Tai-fu either.
What is Brother Bo doing?
He's been lying there for ages.
The autopsy report said something
entered Chin Tai-fu's body
that caused his pacemaker to explode.
I have looked everywhere in this room
and didn't find anything connected.
Ming, lie down.
Me?
Lie down, spreadeagled like I did just now.
Hurry, spread your legs.
You, come here and poke him.
Use your finger.
That's rather x-rated.
Just do it.
Show me the direction.
The wound...the heart...in that direction.
How could Natasha get mixed up
with Chin Tai-fu?
How could he mess with a married woman?
Go to Hell, you jerk!
We bring you the breaking news...
Billionaire Chin Tai-fu was found dead
in Hotel de Maze this morning.
The Police has indicated his cause of death
has yet to be confirmed.
We just received another breaking news.
Businessman Wong Sai-lung was also
found dead inside Hotel de Maze.
He was shot in the head.
It is unknown at the moment whether
their deaths are related.
Wong Sai-lung was the man in charge of
Fullcoin, the recent talk of the town.
Now that he was shot to death,
it's unknown whether his death
is related to the recent Fullcoin incident.
Honey, Wong Sai-lung is dead!
Crap, I'm definitely involved.
Why are you involved?
I told you I found a gun,
and I sold it to someone.
I know. I believe you now.
But it's my problem, not yours.
No, Honey. It's not.
Brother Bo, do you think it looks ruined?
Mosaic feature walls are like that.
Laser pen.
Remember that day we had a fight?
You went inside a room and I was pissed?
I wanted to drink iced water.
Guess what I saw in the ice bucket?
I found a gun.
When the bullet was shot into the wall,
it created friction
that shattered the bullet.
One of the bullet fragments
shot the inner thigh
and caused his pacemaker to explode.
That's the cause of death.
Bravo!
Why didn't you tell me about it?
What happened to the gun?
I was really scared.
I ditched it right away.
Then I filled up the hole with toothpaste.
No wonder there was no toothpaste
in my room.
Look, we didn't kill anyone.
Let's go to the Police station
and tell the Police what happened.
Ming, ask Ms. Yu for the guest information
of this room.
We need to question them.
Got it.
Brother Bo, King said the couple from
the Executive Suite
went to the Police Station.
Honey!
I'm glad you're here.
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
I should care more about you.
I shouldn't hold out on you...
Let me finish...
I didn't mean to...
Listen to me!
I shouldn't be mad at you.
Then none of this would have happened.
No...it was my fault.
Please go to the Crime Unit
to give your statement.
Don't worry, we'll be OK after
we give our statement.
I tried the gun in a room
and then sold it.
Here...
I didn't know there was a gun in the
ice bucket.
My hand was shaking when I picked it up.
I accidentally dropped it on the floor
and the gun went off.
I was really scared.
I was fighting with my husband at the time
and I remembered he said he found
a gun in the hotel
and he sold it later.
I was afraid someone would find the gun
and my husband would get into trouble.
So I took it outside to ditch it.
I remember seeing a laundry cart
in the backstairs of the 10/F.
I decided to leave it in there.
But the cart was gone.
Then I went downstairs to the ground floor,
and put the gun in a laundry bag
inside the cart.
Did Chan Lai-sa make this up?
According to her statement,
even if we don't find the gun,
we don't have enough to nail her.
We're almost certain
Chin Tai-fu was shot because the gun
went off
when Chan Lai-sa dropped it.
The question is where is the gun now
and how many shots are left.
Cheung Tin-fai mentioned
Wong Sai-lung was shot twice in the head.
Then he got too scared and dropped the gun.
It went off and shot Wong Sai-lung again.
Three shots were fired already.
Chin Chi-tat said he fired once
to test the gun.
Plus the shot fired when Chan Lai-sa
dropped the gun,
five shots have been fired.
There should be one bullet left.
Not until we locate the gun,
we're still not safe yet.
If Cheung Tin-fai is not the
white-haired hitman,
who's the real killer?
Where is he hiding?
Would Silver Fox squeal on me?
That's crazy! If he would,
he wouldn't let me go.
I haven't done anything.
I only sold him a few uniforms.
And...I didn't tell anyone I saw a gun.
And...I didn't report Wong Sai-lung's body.
And...I conked Chin Tai-fu on the head.
And...I took his cheque.
I'm dead just from knowing about everything.
Was Fai right about this?
Not until the cops catch the real killer,
we're not off the hook?
I only know the hitman was wearing
the housekeeping uniform.
I didn't even see his face.
How can I find him?
Let's just rip the cheque.
Don't...
A white-haired dude in uniform?
That's too much of a coincidence.
Silver Fox, stop!
Maybe Wong Sai-lung's killer
was that other Silver Fox.
Why did he get into Yu Lo's car?
He colluded with Yu Lo?
That's why Yu Lo was on my case?
No! What if it wasn't him?
If I call the cops, they will arrest me.
Better not!
I'll go to Yu Lo's place and find out
what's going on.
If they're in on this, I'll call the cops.
What happened? Why are you tied up?
I was going out to lunch.
The white-haired dude took me hostage
and made me drive him here
or else he would kill me.
Where is he now?
Trying to save your colleague?
Not you again, Mr. Chan!
What are you talking about?
I mean why do you have the gun again?
I was beaten half to death
and thrown in the garbage bin.
I thought I was going to die.
But I lucked out and came across a gun.
I shouldn't have thrown it in the garbage.
You're now my hostage.
If you step outside the house,
I'll blow her head off.
No...
Be my guest. I'm leaving.
Stay where you are!
Law Siu-fong, don't go. I'm your Boss.
Shut up, Yu Lo. I already quit.
I'm in this mess thanks to you.
Now the Police suspect me
of killing Wong Sai-lung.
You plan to finger me? Go to Hell!
It's empty?
Luck is on my side.
It doesn't hurt!
No blood?
Cuff him!
Thank goodness! Yeah!
Yes, we can live...
Yes, we're alive!
I thought we were going to die!
I was so scared!
Scared me to death...
I'm so scared...
Who's your friend now?
Exactly!
Thanks for your hard work in cracking
this bizarre case.
We didn't realize the gun has been fired
so many times by so many people.
And Law Siu-fong really had nine lives.
Brother Bo, don't be so modest.
You saved Law Siu-fong's life.
You really hit the bullseye.
When he fired the first shot,
the gun was empty.
As for the second shot,
Cheung Tin-fai dropped the bullet
and it went inside the uniform.
The killer grabbed it in the end.
We sent the bullet to Forensics for tests
and found curry sauce on it.
It got stuck in the barrel.
That's why I didn't save Law Siu-fong,
it was the dirty bullet.
I didn't expect so much would happen
by checking into the hotel for a day.
I'm sorry, Honey! I should have trusted you.
You threw the gun away for me
why would you cheat on me?
I should bear some of the blame.
I have given you too much pressure.
I always use material things
to measure our love.
I realized now, none of that matter.
The key is for us to be safe,
and that we are together.
I'm so glad you're OK.
The Police believed you had no intention
to fire that shot
and didn't realize that bullet
would go through the wall
and shoot Chin Tai-fu.
Honey, you won't get a long sentence
for selling the gun.
We'll start over when you get out.
I must thank you for dropping the bullet
in the curry sauce.
The stain was the reason it got stuck.
You indirectly saved my life.
I must thank you.
I didn't realize this unprofessional hitman
did a good thing.
Will I get a lighter sentence for it?
Fai, attempted murder will get
a life sentence.
Now, you only serve a few years.
The jail sentence is nothing.
After everything I did,
I still don't have money in the bank.
Don't say that.
Because Chin Tai-fu is dead,
someone found out he was
the instigator of Fullcoin.
His estate fund agreed to compensate
all the Fullcoin victims.
Really?
Yeah!
When you get out, you'll have money
to pay off your debts.
Thank God!
Yip Wing-kei, a.k.a. the Showbiz King.
Got into a grudge with Chin Tai-fu
over Fullcoiin.
Mr. Yip, your wife and daughter have
boarded the high-speed rail.
I'm putting you up in a hotel.
Royal Island Hotel? Is it safe?
I chose this hotel because of its
tight security and abundant staff.
They can ensure your safety.
Chin Tai-fu's hitmen won't find you.
Bloody hell, the guy is dead
and he's still after me.
Don't worry, Mr. Yip!
I already contacted his wife
to let you off the hook.
Thanks for your advice.
Brother Kei, either you take my money,
and guarantee me and family
will live happily ever after,
or else, if anything should happen to me,
I guarantee I'll use my entire fortune
to kill you.
We can make a lot of money from sucker Kei.
What matters is this can go on forever.
Make sure you count me in.